You have to pick who’ll go out alive now.
I’m sorry.
Tai.
I told you I’d stay with you.
I’ll stay no matter what.
You should get some rest.
What about you?
I’ll go out and get some food for us.
I don’t want to be alone. I’m scared.
I’ll stay til you fall asleep then.
Promise?
Hmm… Now get some rest.
I used to stay here from time to time so there’s some stuff here.
You don’t like rice soup?
Nah.
I want to know what happened
before you came to save me.
Por forced me to work for him.
He used the opportunity to hold you and Phupha in ransom.
Now I’m just trying to get back at him.
Target’s arrived. He’s got a tattoo on his right arm.
Let’s go. Here he comes
Onto the next plan!
Jao!
Believe me he’d say I’ve been drinking and hungover.
Tai! This is Por’s plan.
He’s using us.
What do you mean?
He knows he’s helping Phupha to escape.
He tricked you into doing that job…taking me into ransom.
But I made an escape.
He must be on his way to get Phupha and Kram.
This is Bank - son of Gen. Kriangkrai.
Good job! I knew you’d make it.
Piak, film this!
I’ve got something I want to send to Kriangkrai.
How do you feel now huh?
Heard you’re coming after me?
Just watch this.
Your son’s with me now.
But don’t worry. I’m not gonna hurt him
only if you leave me alone.
Hang on. I think I might want to change my mind.
Haha.
I want to see your face when you get to see this .
How you’d feel seeing your son dying in front of you.
Fuck!
He’s not Bank! This is Ton, son of the boss.
Tai. Are you sure? You’re messing with the big boss!
Who’s the big boss?
You stupid shit. He’s the one behind gray businesses in Rattha
Even Por is threatened by this guy.
Why didn’t you tell me sooner! I should have stopped Tai!!!
Trust me this is the only way we can stop Por.
How?
What’s your plan?
This guy looks nothing like him.
He can tell in a split second.
It’s your job to make them look alike.
OK. Let’s see what I can do.
Shit!! You…Tai!!! Catch him.
Where are they now? Follow them!!!
Now you know what took me so long.
Sorry. I didn’t know..
It’s alright.
Now eat. It won’t taste as good when it gets cold.
OK.
I’m cold.
Take this.
What about you?
I’m OK.
No. You’ll get sick. Let’s tuck under this blanket together.
Come on. I’d feel better this way.
You’ve already helped me a great deal.
This reminds me of the old times -
staying near the fireplace next to someone .
That ‘someone’ is Phupha?
With my dad.
There was a day I went drawing with my dad in the jungle.
We stayed until late
and couldn’t find our way out.
So we sat next to the fireplace together.
It was warm
and….
Tai, what happened to your face?
My friend picked on him.
Is it the one that teases you about your mum?
Yes.
Come here.
Why did you let him bully you?
I beat you because you’re hopeless.
You make a choice - hit him back and let me beat you up.
I don’t want to hurt him.
Bad dreams?
Did  I wake you up?
No. But did you have a bad dream?
No
Now you’re lying again.
Why do you always have to lie?
What now?
Whenever I have a bad dream, dad would do this to ease it away.
No need.
You’ve done so much for me. Don’t worry.
You won’t have bad dreams again tonight.
Thanks.
Hmm.
Tai? Is that you?
Where’s Tai?
w…w…what? I….I…I don’t know.
Stop lying! Tell me where he is.
Hey!! What are you doing here?
Get out! I said get out!!! You can’t go upstairs.
Get down! Where do you think you’re going
Stop! I’ll call the police if you don’t!
Where’s Tai? Hmm?
We really don’t know.
I’ll ask you just one more time. Where’s Tai!!!
That’s it?
I’m full now.
Full?
I must be such a bad cook, babe.
What did you just call me?
You call?
You can throw it in the bin if you don’t want to eat it.
No! Don’t! I’m still eating it.
You don’t have to. You’re already full. Just throw it out.
I still want to eat.
Please. Pleaseeeee..
I said you don’t have to.
I want to. Your fried rice is the best.
Let me eat it. Please. Pleaseeee.
- I’m gonna throw it out
- Hey ! Tai.
I’m gonna throw it out.
I can eat it outside.
No.
- It’s dark now. When can I have it?
-		I said you can’t have it.
Hello son.
Run away!
Just run!!!
Quick !!
Don’t mess with my people .
What would you do to me huh?
Don’t be such a coward.
Don’t miss this one like you did 3 years ago.
Kram.
3 years ago
Kram… what happened?
Tai
Kram.
Krammm.
Why did  you have to kill Kram?
Why the hell did you shoot them?
OK so I killed Kram. Got a problem?
Why!!!!
Because they make you weak.
Kill me!
So you can become the big boss.
Trade my life with you growing up. Do you think it’s worth it?
I’ll never become who you want me to be.
You and me….it’s over!!
Arghhh!!!
If you don’t do it, someone will do it to you.
How many times do I have to repeat myself?
Arghhh!!
I give you one last chance.
Just give in.
You…you!!
You’re not going to give it huh?
Arghhh!!
Men don’t cry.
Keep this in mind. Whoever tries to fuck me up,
You’ll have take it the hard way - even my own son.
Please leave him alone.
He’d saved us many many times. Please.
Please.
No more problem around here, I guess.
I’ve been worrying about you! Where have you been?
You had trouble with Por? What happened?
I’m sorry. I don’t know what to say.
What am I supposed to do about this.
I said no!!
Phupha. Phupha
I don’t care!!
Phupha. Phupha.
I’m really sorry. I’ve tried to stop them.
Jao, what happened?
I need to talk to you. It’s urgent.
Kram’s going to be executed?
What’s with Por?
This isn’t ancient time.
Luckily I escaped and found Jao.
I want to ask for Phupha’s help.
I really want to help but I’ve got a lot on my shoulders.
Tai got the big boss’s son killed.
If something else happens, Khumfah will be in trouble too..
No need to worry about that. Tai has it all planned out.
How?
Por had his people filming when he killed boss’s son.
Though it’s been deleted,
I know you can it back.
Sure. I’ll have my guy deliver it. Same place? Sure
Hey…I told you. They’ll pick it up at the back for sure.
You should get going now before they find out.
I wouldn’t have asked you to bring a laptop
if I wanted just a phone.
You stupid! This is for emergencies.
Haven’t you heard of a back up plan?
Shit! That’s clever.
Never knew you could come up with such idea.
Let’s go now.
Piak!
Fuck!
Piak!!!
You said he wouldn’t be here today.
Jao! Jao!!
มึงเข้ามาทำไมเนี่ยHow did you get in here asshole!!
Asshole!!
Oyyy!!
Next one is on you. Why  are you here?
I’m here to get Piak’s phone.
I want to recover that clip of you shooting boss’s son.
You bastard!!
You tried to mess with me behind my back huh?
I didn’t have to.
Wanna fight? Huh? Huh?
Save it for hell.
You’re the one dying and going to hell, not me.
What the fuck!.
I want to see your expression when you get to see this.
How you’d react to see your son dying right in front of you.
Por went behind your back. He wants to take over Rattha.
Your son found out about it so they had to kill him.
We share the same goal.
I want to take down the one who took the life of your son.
Fuck him Por!!! He bloody killed my son!!!
Boss.
Calm down.
Take it easy.
Take it easy?
Why did you kill my son?
There’s some minor misunderstanding.
I beg you. Please don’t kill me.
Misunderstanding?
Then you need to explain to me. What the fuck happened huh?
It was my fault. I didn’t mean it to happen.
I’m truly sorry. It was my fault. But please don’t kill me.
Fuck you! Whooo.
You made me do this.
Now shoot me!
Great. So I killed the big boss. I can’t run away now.
You make it look like you’ve taken care of it.
Please don’t hurt me. Please. I beg you.
Please let me go.
I beg you. Don’t kill me, please.
Don’t kill me, please.
When are you gonna do it?
Dad.
First step is always the hardest.
- Hey hey hey
- 	Take a deep breath.
Hold your gun tightly…and shoot.
D….Don’t!!
I can’t do it.
You disappoint me to the last minute.
Big slum gang is now yours, son.
What are you doing here?
I miss mum.
Tell me the truth. What really happened?
They teased me about not having a mother.
What do you do when a mosquito bites you?
Kill it.
Yes, kill it.
Because if you don’t, it will keep bothering you.
But the teacher says we shouldn’t bully our friends.
There’s no such thing as friendship.
One day you’ll be taking over my place.
You need to learn how to keep them under your feet.
I’m sorry about your father.
No need.
He’s not my father any more.
Tai.
What are you doing?
I just want to cheer you up.
I said I’m OK.
At the very least, he brought you up.
I understand if you’d be upset and disappointed.
That kinda guy?
Crying? Again? Such a wuss.
How many times do I have to tell you this.
Go to bed now!
Go!!!
I said go!!!!
He misses you a lot…..
and me too.
But don’t worry. I’ll teach him to become a real man.
I told you to go to bed. Why are you still up?!?
Let me tell you this.
When my mum died,
I came to her grave everyday.
He was pissed.
He kept telling me to stop crying..
But you what?
He was also crying too.
Tai….
It’s a funny story.
I know he’s never been a good man throughout his life.
But I can still remember the day I hugged him….right there.
I should be happy that he’s dead.
But I don’t know why I’m this sad.
I’ll stay right here with you no matter what.
If there’s anything I can do to make you feel better,
just tell me. I’ll do anything.