I'm going to sort things out in Bangkok for a few months.
Would you like to come with me?
Who painted them?
Kram…in this world….3 years ago.
So the Kram, in this world, used to date Tai?
Hmm.
And what happened 3 years ago?
How could you miss it
They were on their knees and I was careless.
I've told you! Sympathy weakens people down.
Don't miss it next time.
Yes, dad.
Keep an eye on Tai.
Can I make a call?
Just take a rest.
Kram.
What happened? Kram!
What's wrong with Kram?
His memories of this world are passing onto me.
And….and then what happened?
They all went to Kram's house,
killed his dad,
hurt his mother until she lost her sight
and threatened her not to tell.
Why did you have to kill Kram?
Because he weakened you down.
Kill me.
Take me down. So you can become the leader of Big Sulm.
Trade off my life with your growing up, do you think it's worth it?
In the end, Tai couldn't do it. He couldn't kill his own father.
After that,
Tai resigned from Big Slum gang
and lived a depressing life.
Until he met you.
Met me?
Yes.
Tai is back to life again after he met you.
Can I have this?
Once true love's created in the universe.
No matter how far the distance,  two hearts will find their way to one another
Kram..Let's go
I'm sorry, Phupha
Tai.
What are you here?
I've decided not to go to Bangkok.
I'll stay here with you.
Sorry I was hesitant before.
But now I know how I feel.
I may not be the same Kram you're in love with in the other world.
But I'm this other Kram that loves you.
And although you're not the same Kram I fell in love with.
But I've already fallen for you too.
Do you know how grateful I am that we met.
How much I feel when we're close.
Want to treasure every moment,
every second.
You're always on my mind.
So they say happy times fly fast.
It might be too late before we know it.
I missed the chance to tell you how much I love you.
If I said I love you.
If destiny doesn't part our ways.
If you're still here with me.
I wonder if our hearts want the same thing.
Why am I shirtless?
Don't tell me we……..
Thank you but I'm too exhausted.
Wanna take a shower first?
Can I just go to bed?
You should take a shower.
Hmmm.
I can just take my shirt off and go to bed.
Can you go to bed with me?
Nooo.
Why not?? Let's just go to bed
No.
Come one.
Let's go to bed. Come on now.
OK OK.
You're such a whining baby, aren't you.
Was I really that bad?
Hmm.
Mum said I used to sleep talking a lot.
Never thought it's that bad.
The other Tai is exactly just like you
Hey….be nice. We're dating now.
You should be nicer to me.
What should I call you now?
Babe.
Just Kram should do.
But I want to feel like your little puppy.
Just Kram should be fine.
Nooo. Call me babe.
Kram.
Babe.
Kram!
Tai
What are you up to?
I'm making some soup.
Ouch!
You shouldn't be cooking if you know you're clumsy.
Thanks, bro.
Let me take care of it.
It's ok.
I want to do it…for you.
Here's how you hold a knife. Hold it right, alright?
Then you slide it down like this.
Got it?
Yup.
Eat while it's still hot
Wow. Tastes great.
Have you been in the kitchen much?
Kram I knew…
he likes this dish. So I've been learning how to cook it.
You just can't stop talking about him, can you?
I'm just a nobody.
Don't say that. You two are two different person.
Which Kram do you like more?
Both.
I knew you'd say that.
You're much cuter, babe.
What did you just call me?
I could only say it once.
And you missed it.
Say it again. I didn't hear it clearly. What did you just call me?
Say it one more time….please please.
I'll feed you if you do.
I said I could only say it once.
What now, Jao?
What happened?
Phupha….Phupha has been kidnapped!
I'm taking Janda to see her mum in Chiangmai for a week.
Do you want anything on my way back?
No worries, dad. Have fun.
Wayu, make a u-turn.
Where do you want to head to?
Do you think it's a good idea?
So it means…..
Janda's planning to kill me.
Get Chat and Aom to dig dirt on Janda. Check the tape…
Mr.Phupha!! Ouch
Wayu!!!
Stop!!!
They've escaped.
Let them go for now.
I've been digging dirt on who's been trying to take you down.
But I couldn't find anything. Never thought it would turn out to be Janda.
Well then dad must be…..
About your father and I …. I'll take care of it.
But we haven't got enough evidence.
Phupha's nearly killed in his home. That's enough proof already.
Then I'll just leave it with you.
Yes, auntie.
Your father and Janda have confessed.
What??
They've made a confession. All they've done is because they don't want you to become a successor.
Janda and dad just found out not long ago I'm not the real son.
That's why they've been threatening me not to take up the position?
Yes. But I guess it's because you didn't back down.
So now they want to have you killed.
And….you also knew?
I've been raising you like my own baby.
Though we're not related biologically,
but I do love you very much
Thank you so much.
If you're ever in need for help from now on, you don't have to say it out loud. This is what you have to do.
Tie your laces up into double knots.
I'll tell you teacher what it means
So they know you need their help.
I need to go to the restroom.
Find a way to escape. Aunty is the bad guy.
How are you planning to run away?
Don't worry. I'll find a way.
You….you've poisoned me?
How do you know?
Shoe..laces.
Oh…so that's he tied up my laces.
Can't help you much now that you know
Sorry, Phupha.
Everyone in Khumfah reports directly to Satreekij now
I don't know who I can ask for help. That's why I'm here. I need your help
Janda.
I used to hate you so much.
The wiser you are, the more it makes me look dumb.
But when I think about it now, you've never really said anything bad to me.
So I guess I don't hate you that much after all.
Mr.Phupha is up now, Maam.
I'll be there.
Phupha!
Phupha.
I've told you to take me instead!! What has my child got to do with this, huh?
You dragged Phupha into this mess.
If you hadn't tried to tie up my laces,
he would have not been here.
Why are you doing this? I thought we're family.
Family? You call this a family? Family full of hatred.
Bullshit!!
I've given your father so many chances.
But he's too stupid to realize it.
Arghh
What a stupid move making you a successor instead of me.
I'm his blood sister!!
It's time for me to get back what's mine.
Exactly when did you find out that I'm not your real son?
Your mother wrote a confession letter
when you were 7….
Before she took her life.
25 years ago
It all began when mum was dating Wiroj, your real father.
Why?
Don't you love me?
Yes.
I'm not in love with you.
I'm in love with Adisak.
Adisak.
I've got something to tell you.
I've been thinking about it. I think…..
Who is it?
Sorry. I never meant to hide it but I haven't had a chance to tell Rojana.
We're about to have a child together.
Ummm…
Ummm. I'm really happy for you both.
Then your parents got married.
I never realized that baby was Wiroj's .
Dad…are you back? I've missed you.
I was shocked. I didn't know what to do.
What's wrong? Are you hurt?
I'm OK.
Now remember this.
No matter what happens,
I love you you	And I always will.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry I doubted you..
No problem. No problem at all, Phupha.
I love you very much.
I love you too,
Dad!!
Phupha, are you in there?
Yup.
You guys wait here. I'll take care of it.
Let me come with you.
I can't risk it.
But I'm the one who brought everyone to risk. If something happens to you….
I'll be OK.
Promise you'll come back to me?
I promise.
Jao!
Yes?
Take care of Kram for me.
Sure will.
Satreekij you bitch!
What have you done to Janda? You bitch!!!!
Aren't you guys hungry?  I've prepared your favorites.
I've got your favorite too, Janda. Try it! It's really nice.
Do you know why you're still alive?
You still love us?
You can't talk me into it with your sweet talk.
I won't let you go this time.
But now that I think of it. If you died, I'll become the first suspect.
So I think I might stab you first, then your dad
Then the police will think you two get into a fight…and kill one another.
Khumfah will be mine.
Don't you just feel like celebrating for me?
We haven't had drinks together in such a long time.
Let's make a toast.
How do you feel being taken down the same way too?
Mr.Phupha!
Chat! How did you get here?
I'm here to help you escape. Let's go.
Arghhh
Chat! You….
Can you remember me?
Dad! Run away!!
But you….
Go! Run! Get someone's help!!
Since when have you been betraying behind my back?
Betray? I've been on Satreekij's side since the beginning.
Tai!
You again?
Good! Now I take a revenge for my brother.
Asshole!!
Boss!! Where's Mr.Phupha?
He's in a fight with Chat inside…
Chat…that guy has been betraying us.
What about Tai!!!
Argh!!!
Kram! Where do you think you're going?
I'm going to save Tai.
It's too dangerous.
Tai's in danger!!
Kram.
I need to help Tai.
Kram…Kram!!
Just calm down.
Tai.
I thought you'd never come back.
I made my promise.
What are you staring at.
I'm just happy..that you're still here with me.
I'm afraid of losing my loved one.
I didn't think I'd make it that night either.
But I thought of the promise I gave you.
So I fought to the last minute.
And it made me realize…
What is it?
You're the one that makes me want to live my life a long long time.
I wouldn't ask for anything else but you.
Join the Ash Ceremony with me.
You don't have to decide now.
I know you've got a lot on your mind.
I can wait.
So they say happy times fly fast.
It might be too late before we know it.
I missed the chance to tell you how much I love you
If I said I love you.
If destiny doesn't part our ways
If you're still here with me.
I wonder if our hearts want the same thing
I don't want to be in a world without you
Only if I could turn back time. Only if I got to see you one more time
Don't want to be in a dream that would never come true